And in the death of her reputation, she felt truly alive.
Taylor Swift: Reputation Stadium Tour is a music film directed by Paul Dugdale.
Taylor Swift takes the stage in Dallas for the Reputation Stadium Tour and
celebrates a monumental night of music, memories and visual magic.
Self, played by Taylor Swift.
Self, played by Charli xcx.
Self, played by Camila Cabello.
Self, played by David Cook.
Self, played by Amos Heller.
Self, played by Eliotte Woodford.
The Reputation Stadium Tour was the fifth concert tour and the first all-stadium tour by the American
singer-songwriter Taylor Swift, in support of her sixth studio album, Reputation (2017).
It began in Glendale, Arizona, United States, on May 8, 2018, and
concluded in Tokyo, Japan, on November 21, 2018.
The tour encompassed 53 shows and visited 7 countries in total.
The set list consisted mostly of the songs from
Reputation and some from Swift's other albums.
The stage incorporated prominent snake motifs and imagery as decoration,
reflecting the album's concept and Swift's public image.
The main stage had a wedge-shaped display resembling a skyscraper under construction and was equipped with
elaborate lighting, and two smaller B-stages were used for acoustic “surprise song” performances.
The October 6, 2018, show at AT&T Stadium in Arlington, Texas, was recorded and released as a Netflix original
concert film on December 31, 2018; it has since been removed from Netflix for unknown reasons.
Music critics commented that the production evoked Goth subculture and Broadway
theatricality, praising the stage design, production, and wardrobe.
They lauded Swift's showmanship and interactions with her audience that
brought forth an exhilarating yet intimate experience.
The Reputation Stadium Tour received 2.88 million attendees and grossed $345.6 million,
becoming the highest-grossing US and North American tour upon completion.
It was awarded Tour of the Year at the People's Choice Awards,
American Music Awards, and iHeartRadio Music Awards.
The film explores themes of concert, live performance, concert film.